const qBank = [
  {
    question:
      "কে দ্বিতীয় খলিফা?   ",
    answers: ["ইব্রাহিম", "ওমর (রাঃ)", "আদম()", "উসমান (রাঃ)"],
    correct: "ওমর (রাঃ)",
    questionId: "099099"
  },
  {
    question:
    'Who was the first caliph of islam',
    answers: ["Hazrat Ali (R)", "Hazrat Usman (R)", "Hazrat Umar (R)", "Hazrat Abu Bakar"],
    correct: "Hazrat Abu Bakar",
    questionId: "183452"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the meaning of arabic word siddique?",
      answers : ["The one who believe",
        "The one who doesnt believe",
        "The one who is a good warrior",
        "The one who prays"],
        
    correct: "The one who believe",
    questionId: "267908"
  },
  {
    question:"Who was the 1st ambassador of islam to Madina?",
    answers: ["Hazrat Mus’ab(R)"," Hazrat Abu Huraira (R) ",  
      "Hazrat Ubaid  (R) ",  "Hazrat uk’ba  "],
      
    correct: "Hazrat Mus’ab(R)",
    questionId: "333247"
  },
 
  {
    question: "The miracle journey of prophet (sm) held at",
    answers : ["8th year of his prophethood",
      "5th year of his prophethood",
      "10th year of his prophethood",
      "12th  year of his prophethood"],
      
    correct: "10th year of his prophethood",
    questionId: "2838920"
  },
  {
  question: "At present Masjidul Aksa is situated at?" ,
  answers : ["Soudi Arabia "," Iraq "," Iran","Palestine"],
  correct: "Palestine",
  questionId: "2838901"
  },
  {
    question:"Which is the first qibla of islam?",
  answers : ["Qaba sharif", "Masjid e nababi",  
   "Masjidul Aksa", " Masjidul Mecca"],
   correct: "Masjidul Aksa",
   questionId: "2838921"
  },
  {

    question:"Hazrat Mus’ab (pbuh) accepted islam on the ___ year of prophethood of prophet (sm)?",
  answers : ["2nd"  ," 3rd", "4th", " 5th"], 
  correct: "4th",
  questionId: "2838902"
  },
  
  
  {
  
    question: "What is the meaning of arabic word Asadullah?",
  answers : ["The tiger of Allah",
  "The lion of Allah",
  "The kobra of Allah",
  "The elephant of Allah"],
  correct: "The lion of Allah",
  questionId: "2838903"
  },

  {
  
    question:"Who was the third caliph of islam?",
  answers : ["Hazrat Abu Bakar (R)", "Hazrat Umar (R)","Hazrat Osman(R)"],
  correct: "Hazrat Osman(R)",
  questionId: "2838904"
  
  },
  {
  question:"Asadullah was the title of?",
  answers : [" Hazrat Umar  (R) ", "Hazrat Abu Huraira (R) ", 
  " Hazrat Ubaid ",  "Hazrat Hamza"],
  correct: "Hazrat Hamza",
  questionId: "2838905"
  },
  
  {
  question:"Which is the 69th sura of Holy quaran?",
  answers : ["Sura Al haqqah",  "Sura taha",   
  "Sura takasur",  " Sura bani israil"],
  correct: "Sura Al haqqah",
  questionId: "2838966"
  },

  {
  
  question:"Hazrat Hamza (R) was ___ of prophet (Sm)?",
  answers : ["Uncle",   " Cousin",   " Brother in law", " nephew"],
  correct: "Uncle",
  questionId: "2838907"
  },
  {
  question:"What is the meaning of Allahu Akber?",
  answers : ["Allah hears every thing",
  "Allah can do every thing",
  "Allah is greatest",
  "Allah is mind reader"],
  correct: "Allah is greatest",
  questionId: "28389008"
  },

  {
  question: "Hazrat Ibrahim (pbuh) was ?",
  answers : ["5th generation after Nu’ah (pbuh)",
  "10th generation after Nu’ah (pbuh)",
  "15th generation after Nu’ah (pbuh)",
  "20th generation after Nu’ah (pbuh)"],
  correct: "10th generation after Nu’ah (pbuh)",
  questionId: "2838909"
  },

  {
    question:"Hazrat Ibrahim (pbuh) was born in ?",
  answers : ["Madina ",  " Mecca",  "Babylon",  " Zerusalem"],
  correct: "Babylon",
  questionId: "28389010"
  },
  {

    question:"The father of Hazrat Ibrahim (pbuh) was ?",
  answers : ["Carpenter" ,  "idol maker",  "big farmer ",   "teacher"],
  correct: "idol maker",
  questionId: "2838911"
  },

  {
    question: "Hazrat Lut (pbuh) was ___ of Hazrat Ibrahim (pbuh) ?",
    answers :["Nephew"," Niece ",  " Brother ",  "Uncle"],
    correct: "Nephew",
    questionId: "2838912"
  },

  {
    question: "The black stone (Hazre Asoad) that is kept in Qa’ba , came from?",
    answers :["Heaven"   , " Hell  ", " Zerusalem ", "Babylon"],
  correct: "Heaven",
  questionId: "2838913"
  },

  {
  question: "Hazrat Ibrahim (pbuh) was ?",
  answers :["about 150 years  ", "about 175 years",   
  "about 200 years",  "about 200 years",
  "When the,Youth", "Old "," very old"],
  correct: "about 175 years",
  questionId: "2838914"
  },

  {
    question: "Mother of Hazrat Ismail (pbuh)?",
    answers :[ "Hazrat Saira (pbuh)  ", "Hazrat Hazera (pbuh)",
       " Hazrat Asiya (pbuh) ", " Hazrat Morium (pbuh)"],
       correct: "Hazrat Hazera (pbuh)",
       questionId: "2838915"
  },

  

  {
    question:"After the rain and storm, the people of Hud (pbuh) migrated to ?",
    answers :[" Iraq    ", "Iran",   " Yemen",  " Oman"],
    correct: "Yemen",
    questionId: "2838917"
  },

  {
  question:"The number of Maqqi sura in the holy q’uaran is ?",
  answers : [" 86",    " 20. ",  " 36",   "76"],
  correct: "86",
  questionId: "2838918"
  },
  {

  question:"The Eid ul Azha takes place on ?",
  answers : ["1st Zilkad  ",   "10th Zilkad",
  "1st zilhajj ",  "10th Zilhajj"],
  correct: "10th Zilhajj",
  questionId: "2838919"
  }
  
  
];

export default (n = 20) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
